[rock music]
【摇滚音乐】
[man on TV] Don't be afraid to sing, Dragon.
【电视上的男人】别害怕唱歌，Dragon。
[Dragon on TV] But what if I burn someone?
【电视上的Dragon】但如果我烧伤了别人呢？
[man on TV] But what if you don't?
【电视上的男人】但如果你没有呢？
[all] ♪ So sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
【所有人】♪ 所以大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！♪
- ♪ Every voice ♪ - Kids, who wants lunch?
【- ♪ 每个声音 ♪】- 孩子们，谁想要午餐？
♪ Deserves a crowd, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 都值得被聆听，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- Grilled cheese okay? - ♪ Every voice is beautiful ♪
- 奶酪三明治可以吗？【- ♪ 每个声音都很美 ♪】
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
Oh, that Dragon Breath movie again.
哦，又是那部《Dragon Breath》电影。
[sighs] - ♪ Every breath you take is precious ♪
[叹气] - ♪ 每一次呼吸 ♪ ♪ 你都珍贵 ♪
- I bet you'd listen if I talked like a dragon. - ♪ Every song you sing is gold ♪
- 我打赌如果你像龙一样说话，你会听的。 - ♪ 你唱的每一首歌 ♪ ♪ 都是金子 ♪
♪ Every note you play is magical ♪
♪ 你弹奏的每一个音符 ♪ ♪ 都是魔法 ♪
Apparently you won't.
显然你不会。
Those kids do not listen.
那些孩子根本不听。
- It's so frustrating. - I know.
- 真是令人沮丧。 - 我知道。
It's like that movie has stolen our children.
就好像那部电影偷走了我们的孩子。
None of the apps on my phone are working.
我手机上的所有应用都不工作了。
And tech support has stolen my husband.
而技术支持偷走了我的丈夫。
No, no, no, don't put me on hold.
不，不，不，别让我等待。
Don't put me on hold--
别让我等——
Great, they put me on hold.
好吧，他们让我等着了。
Do you know what it's like to be ignored, Anne?
你知道被忽视是什么感觉吗，安妮？
[all] ♪ So sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
♪ 所以大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！♪
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被听见 ♪
I don't know what's more annoying--
我不知道哪个更烦人——
constantly being put on hold,
不停地被搁置，
or constantly hearing that song.
还是不停地听到那首歌。
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
♪ So sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
♪ 所以大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！♪
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被聆听 ♪
Definitely that song.
绝对是那首歌。
♪ Every voice is beautiful, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 每个声音都是美丽的，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
♪ Every noise is musical, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 每个噪音都是音乐，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
Can you guys turn that off?
你们能关掉那个吗？
I'm trying to hear the hold music!
我正试着听等待音乐呢！
Hey, Dad, why don't you just
嘿，爸爸，你为什么不直接
go to the phone store at the mall?
去商场里的电话店呢？
- It'll be faster. - That's a great idea.
那样会更快。- 那是个好主意。
- We're going to the mall. - Great, have fun.
我们要去商场了。- 好，玩得开心。
- You kids are coming with us. [all] Ugh!
你们这些孩子要跟我们一起去。
Guys, you can't stay home alone,
伙计们，你们不能独自留在家里，
and you have seen this movie enough.
而且你们已经看过这部电影太多次了。
Let's go.
走吧。
[all] Ugh! - Hey, hey, hey, hey,
哎！
your mom's right. You need to get away from that Dragon Breath song.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，
[through phone speaker] ♪ So sing out loud ♪ - Oh! No! - ♪ Sing out proud ♪
你们妈妈说得对。你们需要远离那首《龙息》歌。
[sighs]
♪ 所以大声唱出来 ♪
[kids] ♪ Sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
哦！不！
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 自豪地唱出来 ♪
[both] Ugh!
[both] 唉！
[upbeat music]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na, hey! ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦，嘿！♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping]
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪
♪ 纳纳纳纳纳-纳，嘿！ ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
- ♪ 一二 ♪ - ♪ 纳纳纳纳纳-纳 ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一二三四！ ♪
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
Okay, I'll get us a number.
好的，我会给我们一个号码。
[kids] Ugh!
[孩子们] 唉！
51.
51。
Oh! See? We're only four numbers away.
哦！看？我们只差四个号码。
This thing's always acting up.
这东西总是出问题。
[all] Ugh!
[所有人] 唉！
We're gonna be stuck in the mall forever.
我们会被困在商场里永远出不去。
Let's try and be positive.
让我们试着保持积极的态度。
The mall's not that bad.
商场也没那么糟糕。
How would we know?
我们怎么知道？
We're not in the mall.
我们不在商场里。
The mall's out there.
商场在外面。
And we're stuck here. In a store.
而我们被困在这里。在一家店里。
Watching our parents run an errand,
看着我们的父母跑腿，
like we always are.
就像我们总是那样。
We're gonna be here forever, Anne.
我们会一直在这里，安妮。
And we didn't have lunch.
而且我们还没吃午饭。
First my apps, now my appetite.
先是我的应用程序，现在连食欲都没了。
What's the point of anything?
做任何事情有什么意义呢？
What's the point of anything...
做任何事情有什么意义呢...
if we can't be out there... like them?
如果我们不能像他们那样在外面...
- Free. - Without parents.
自由自在。
Having fun.
没有父母在身边。
You know what?
享受乐趣。
We need to take a stand.
你知道吗？
- Got it.
我们需要采取行动。
Now what?
现在怎么办？
No.
不行。
This is the day we ask Mom and Dad
今天我们要向爸爸妈妈提出
to let us go free in the mall!
让我们在商场自由活动的请求！
But they're just gonna say no.
但他们肯定会说不的。
But what if they don't?
但如果他们不呢？
I'm just gonna walk up and say it.
我打算直接走过去说出来。
Oh, please.
哦，拜托。
You're not the "walk up and say it" type.
你不是那种‘直接走过去说出来’的类型。
Let me handle this.
让我来处理这件事。
Uh, what do you mean?
呃，你什么意思？
I'm always walking up and saying stuff.
我总是走过去说些什么的。
Watch me.
看着我。
Mom, I just wanted to walk up and say...
妈妈，我只是想走过去说...
When I become a mom, I want to be just like you.
当我成为妈妈时，我想像你一样。
Oh, sweetie.
哦，亲爱的。
Say it.
说吧。
And let my kids go free in the mall.
让我的孩子们在商场里自由活动。
- Alone. - Alone?
- 独自。 - 独自？
Not alone. Together.
不是独自。一起。
But without you.
但是没有你。
- Without me? - Not without you.
- 没有我？ - 不是没有你。
Well--well, yes, without you.
嗯--嗯，是的，没有你。
We're taking a stand!
我们在表明立场！
But my babies?
但是我的孩子们？
Alone in the mall?
独自在商场里？
We're not babies. Together we're over 40.
我们不是小孩子。我们一起已经超过40岁了。
And over 40 is a very mature age.
而且超过40岁是一个非常成熟的年龄。
[grunts] Ka-bah!
[咕哝] 卡巴！
This town is big enough for the both of us.
这个镇子足够大，容得下我们两个。
Oh, no, when your dad gets hungry he buys up
哦，不，你爸爸一饿就会把
everything in sight.
眼前的东西全买光。
- Yee-haw! - Okay, you know what?
- 耶哈！ - 好吧，你知道吗？
I--I have to stay here and keep an eye on your trigger-happy pappy.
我——我得留在这儿看着你那容易冲动的爸爸。
So, uh, I guess you can go.
所以，呃，我想你可以走了。
[all] Yes!
（所有人）耶！
But he's gonna need some food.
但他会需要些吃的。
So here-- here's some money.
所以这里——这里有些钱。
- Cool. No problem. - Thanks.
- 酷。没问题。 - 谢谢。
- Love you, Mom. - No, no, no, no. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hold on.
- 爱你，妈妈。 - 不，不，不，不。嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，等等。
I have some ground rules, so I need you to listen.
我有一些基本规则，所以需要你听好。
Stay together. Don't talk to strangers.
待在一起。不要和陌生人说话。
[Dawn voice-over] First time alone in the mall without parents!
第一次在没有父母的情况下独自在商场！
[Ricky voice-over] Freedom! Sweet, sweet freedom!
自由！甜蜜的自由！
[Dicky voice-over] Mall chicks. Sweet, sweet mall chicks.
商场里的女孩们。甜蜜的商场女孩们。
[Nicky voice-over] I see Mom's lips moving,
我看到妈妈的嘴唇在动，
so she must think I'm listening.
所以她一定以为我在听。
But I'm totally not listening.
但我完全没有在听。
[Anne] And don't load up at the makeup counter,
还有，不要在化妆品柜台买太多，
don't get lotion in your eyes,
不要让乳液进到眼睛里，
don't get hit by a helicopter,
不要被直升机撞到，
and, I can't believe I'm saying this, but don't lose your pants.
而且，我简直不敢相信我得这么说，但别把裤子弄丢了。
- You got all that? - Yup.
- 你都记住了吗？ - 嗯。
- Got it. - Every word.
- 明白了。 - 每个字都记住了。
100%.
100%。
Well, in case you weren't listening,
好吧，万一你刚才没在听，
I'm writing down the most important thing.
我正在写下最重要的事情。
Okay! Be back in 30 minutes.
好的！30分钟后回来。
- Thank you for trusting us. - We won't let you down. - Don't worry, Mom.
- 谢谢你信任我们。 - 我们不会让你失望的。 - 别担心，妈妈。
Nothing's gonna go wrong.
什么都不会出错的。
How did it go so wrong so fast?
怎么这么快就出错了？
We probably shouldn't have split up.
我们可能不应该分开。
How did that happen?
这是怎么发生的？
I was at the flying toy kiosk,
我当时在飞玩具摊位，
and I did not see it coming.
我完全没有预料到。
How did that happen?
这是怎么发生的？
I went a little crazy at the lotion kiosk.
我在润肤露摊位有点失控了。
Ow, it still burns!
哎哟，现在还烧得慌！
How'd you get lotion in your eyes?
你怎么会把润肤露弄到眼睛里？
It's not just in my eyes.
不只是眼睛里。
It's in the ducts!
它进到泪管里了！
Just be glad you can't see Dawn's makeup.
你该庆幸看不到Dawn的妆容。
Hey, I was at the makeup counter,
嘿，我在化妆品柜台，
and the lady gave me a makeover.
那里的女士给我化了妆。
More like a make over, and over, and over.
更像是化了又化，化了又化。
Says the guy with no pants.
说这话的人连裤子都没穿。
How could you lose your pants?
你怎么会连裤子都丢了？
I didn't lose 'em.
我没丢。
I left them on the dressing room floor.
我把它们留在试衣间的地板上了。
- Why? - 'Cause that's where
为什么？因为那才是它们该待的地方。
they belong.
它们就该在那儿。
When I tried on a pair of Chunk-a-relli jeans,
当我试穿一条Chunk-a-relli牛仔裤时，
it was like taking my legs on an exotic vacation.
感觉就像带着我的双腿去了一次异国旅行。
I thought it was pronounced Ciancarelli.
我以为它的发音是Ciancarelli。
Isn't it See-in-sa-relli?
不是See-in-sa-relli吗？
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
It's pronounced "go get your pants!"
它的发音是“快去拿你的裤子！”
Not doing it.
我才不呢。
Once you've wrapped your trunk in some Chunks,
一旦你用Chunk-a-relli裹住你的双腿，
there's no going back.
就再也回不去了。
But you can't walk around the mall like that.
但你就这样在商场里走？
Okay.
好吧。
Well, at least we'll know our way around.
嗯，至少我们能熟悉一下环境。
See? Cool and helpful.
看吧？既酷又实用。
Really? You're gonna walk around the mall in a sarong?
真的吗？你打算穿着纱笼逛商场？
Hey, if this is sarong, I don't wanna be right.
嘿，如果这就是纱笼，那我可不想正确。
Okay, look, we have 20 minutes to get Dad's food.
好了，听着，我们只有20分钟去给爸爸买吃的。
Where's the food court?
美食广场在哪儿？
Hold still, Dicky.
别动，迪基。
It looks like it's just above his knee.
看起来刚好在他的膝盖上方。
To just above his knee!
到他膝盖上方！
- These are great. - Nope. No, absolutely not.
- 这些很棒。 - 不，绝对不行。
Look at this. This is the coolest--
看看这个，这是最酷的——
- Tom, stop. - We gotta get these--
- 汤姆，停下。 - 我们得拿到这些——
Honey, no. Put that down.
亲爱的，不，放下那个。
- Please. - No, look, I'm--I'm starving.
- 请。 - 不，听着，我——我快饿死了。
Ow, the hunger pains are getting sharper.
哎哟，饥饿感越来越强烈了。
I don't know what childbirth feels like,
我不知道生孩子是什么感觉，
but I'm pretty sure this is worse.
但我敢肯定这比那更糟糕。
Honey, if you say that one more time,
亲爱的，如果你再说一次，
these women are gonna show you
这些女士们会准确地向你展示
exactly what childbirth feels like.
分娩是什么感觉。
Oh! #49! Sweetie, we're so close.
哦！49号！亲爱的，我们快到了。
Ahh!
啊！
- Where is the food court? - I don't know.
- 美食广场在哪里？ - 我不知道。
It's hard to follow a map when it's running.
跑动时很难看地图。
Wait. [sniffs]
等等。[嗅]
Corn dogs.
玉米热狗。
This way.
这边。
Hey, you guys wanna try some hand lotion samples?
嘿，你们想试试手部乳液样品吗？
Do I?
我吗？
You again? I already cut you off.
又是你？我已经拒绝过你了。
What? I can handle my lotion!
什么？我可懂得如何使用护手霜！
Sorry about him.
对不起，别理他。
Hey, don't you go to my high school?
嘿，你不是在我那所高中上学吗？
Really? You think I go to high school?
真的？你觉得我会在上高中？
She's 11.
她才11岁。
Oh, wow,
哦，哇，
- then that's a lot of makeup. - Thanks!
那你化了很多妆呢。
Hey Jaymis,
谢谢！
that cute girl Randee's working Lost and Found today.
那个可爱的女孩Randee今天在失物招领处工作。
Sweet.
真好。
Yo, Aramis, you have to help me lose something
嘿，Aramis，你得帮我丢点东西，
so I can say, "Hey, girl. I lost something."
这样我就可以说，'嘿，女孩。我丢了点东西。'
Hey, I'm watching you, Moist Mitts.
嘿，我盯着你呢，Moist Mitts。
Okay, there's the food court.
好的，那里是美食广场。
Does anyone have any of Mom's money left?
有人还剩下妈妈的钱吗？
I spent mine on the helicopter.
我把我的花在直升机上了。
Lip gloss.
唇彩。
I bought a Chunk-a-relli pocket.
我买了一个Chunk-a-relli口袋。
It's a $5 slice of heaven.
这是5美元的天堂切片。
I bought a fake mustache.
我买了一个假胡子。
For what?
为了什么？
More losh. They're on to me.
更多的烟雾弹。他们盯上我了。
Hey, hey--oh.
嘿，嘿——哦。
Oh, I'm sorry, sir. Pump away.
哦，对不起，先生。请继续加油。
Now, if we don't find someway to get Dad's food,
现在，如果我们找不到办法弄到爸爸的食物，
we'll never be alone in the mall again.
我们就再也不能在商场里独处了。
Yeah, they'll be pushing us around
是啊，他们会推着我们
in those little fire trucks
在那些小消防车上
for the rest of our lives.
余生都要这样了。
- We need to get some money. - But how?
- 我们需要弄些钱。 - 但是怎么弄？
Hmm...
嗯...
[all] Hmm...
[所有人] 嗯...
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
Anybody got anything?
有人有什么主意吗？
Just these soft, supple hands.
只有这些柔软、有弹性的手。
[sighs]
[叹气]
Well, think harder!
再想想！
Ow!
哎哟！
What are you laughing at, helicopter?
你在笑什么，直升机？
Ow!
哎哟！
I got it!
我明白了！
We launch corn dogs into space
我们可以把玉米热狗发射到太空
and get Martians hooked!
让火星人上瘾！
How is that gonna help us get money to buy Dad's food?
这怎么帮我们赚钱买爸爸的食物？
It's not. It's just an awesome idea!
不帮。这只是个很棒的主意！
[applause]
[掌声]
[gasps] Dragon Breath! That's it!
[吸气] 《龙息》！就是这样！
Everyone loves that song!
大家都喜欢那首歌！
- Give me your pocket. - Give me your lip gloss.
- 把你的口袋给我。 - 把你的唇彩给我。
This isn't a swap meet. It's part of the plan.
这不是交换会。这是计划的一部分。
Now, follow my lead.
现在，跟着我做。
All right, everyone.
好了，各位。
Time to keep the in-mall entertainment going.
是时候继续商场内的娱乐活动了。
Time to sing out strong!
是时候大声唱出来了！
[all] ♪ Sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
♪ 大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！♪
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被聆听 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, every voice is beautiful ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，每个声音都很美妙 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
♪ Every noise is musical, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 每个声音都是音乐，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
Excuse me. Excuse me.
不好意思，不好意思。
My Frankie sings that song all the time...
我的弗兰基总是唱这首歌...
[all] Aw.
哎呀。
And I hate it.
我讨厌它。
So if I give you $10, will you stop?
所以如果我给你10美元，你能停下来吗？
But what if we don't?
但如果我们不停呢？
[all] ♪ Sing out loud! ♪
♪ 大声唱出来！♪
- ♪ Sing out proud! ♪ - $20?
♪ 骄傲地唱出来！♪ - 20美元？
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被聆听，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
How about $30?
30美元怎么样？
Make it $50... and we'll throw in a boy.
50美元吧...再加一个小男孩。
Your pick.
你选。
We'll take $30.
我们接受30美元。
Guys, it worked!
伙计们，成功了！
We got 30 bucks to stop singing.
我们得到了30美元，不用再唱歌了。
Now we just have to get Dad's food.
现在我们只需要拿到爸爸的食物。
Do any of you remember what Mom wanted us to get him?
你们有人记得妈妈让我们给他买什么吗？
I don't know, I wasn't listening.
我不知道，我没在听。
Me, neither.
我也是。
That's probably what she wrote on the note.
那她可能写在纸条上了。
- Who's got it? - Me! It's in my pants!
谁拿着纸条？我！在我裤子里！
Oh, that's great,
哦，太好了，
it's in your pants that you're not wearing!
在你没穿的裤子里！
How could Mom leave us alone in the mall?
妈妈怎么能让我们单独在商场里呢？
- We weren't ready for this! - We're just her babies!
我们还没准备好！我们只是她的宝宝！
Calm down.
冷静点。
There is no need to freak out.
没必要惊慌。
All we have to do is go to that store and get your pants back.
我们只需要去那家店把你的裤子拿回来。
Come on.
快点。
Okay, so your pants are gone.
好吧，所以你的裤子不见了。
- Can we freak out now? - Yeah.
- 我们现在可以慌了吗？ - 是的。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
Hold on, hold on.
等等，等等。
If your pants aren't there,
如果你的裤子不在那里，
then maybe they're in the Lost and Found.
那么也许它们在失物招领处。
I think we should just go tell Mom and Dad what's going on.
我认为我们应该去告诉爸爸妈妈发生了什么。
No! We can't let them know we've messed up.
不！我们不能让他们知道我们搞砸了。
Yeah. Let's just go to the Lost and Found
是的，我们去失物招领处看看，
and see if we can find Dicky's pants.
找找Dicky的裤子。
Where's the Lost and Found?
失物招领处在哪儿？
Um, turn around, Dicky.
嗯，转过身来，Dicky。
It's in this area by his derriere.
就在他屁股后面的这个地方。
To his dairy area!
到他的奶制品区去！
♪ Sing out loud, sing out proud ♪
♪ 大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来 ♪
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被聆听 ♪
Ugh, that song is so annoying.
唉，这首歌真烦人。
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
"No unattended children."
禁止无人看管的儿童。
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
[phone rings]
[电话铃响]
Hello, you lose 'em, we find 'em!
你好，你丢了他们，我们找到他们！
Oh, hey girl. Yeah, they make me say that.
哦，嘿，女孩。是的，他们让我这么说。
Who says we're all children?
谁说我们都是孩子？
Watch your teenage sister work her magic.
看你十几岁的妹妹施展她的魔法。
What do you think I should do with my hair?
你觉得我应该怎么处理我的头发？
Should I pony it up?
我应该扎个马尾吗？
Hey, girl. Cute hair.
嘿，女孩。可爱的发型。
You should totally pony that up.
你完全应该扎个马尾。
So here's the sitch.
情况是这样的。
I'm in charge of my way-younger bros,
我要负责照顾比我小很多的弟弟们,
and one of 'em lost his pair of pants.
其中一个把裤子弄丢了。
My mom will totally freak and blame me
如果我们找不到，我妈肯定会抓狂，然后怪到我头上。
if we don't find them.
青少年的问题，对吧？
Teenage problems, am I right?
妈妈们啊。
Moms.
等等，你多大了？
Wait, how old are you?
呃...
Uhh...
嘿，你是兰迪，失物招领兰迪。
Hey, you're Randee. Lost-and-Found Randee.
嘿，你是兰迪。失物招领处的兰迪。
You've heard of me?
你听说过我？
People have heard of me.
人们听说过我。
Yah, I heard this guy Aramis tell this other guy Jaymis--
是的，我听这个叫阿拉米斯的家伙告诉另一个叫杰米斯的家伙——
Jaymis? Hand losh Jaymis?
杰米斯？手残杰米斯？
Because there's like five Jaymises.
因为大概有五个杰米斯。
There's sunglass cart Jaymis,
有卖太阳镜的杰米斯，
candy store Jaymis, fro-yo Jaymis--
糖果店的杰米斯，冻酸奶的杰米斯——
This was totes losh Jaymis.
这个绝对是手残杰米斯。
TLJ? OMG! TTFN.
TLJ？我的天！拜拜。
- Deets. - Paish.
- 细节。 - 啪。
He was all, "Randee's cute." And Aramis was like,
他当时说，“Randee很可爱。”然后Aramis就像，
"Whatcha gonna do?" And Jaymis was like,
“你要做什么？”Jaymis就像，
"Lose something just so I can say
“失去一些东西只是为了我能说
- 'Hey.'" - Shut. Up.
- ‘嘿。’” - 闭嘴。
- I. Won't. - Then don't.
- 我不会。 - 那就别。
- I'm not. - Seri?
- 我没有。 - 真的？
- So. - No.
- 所以。 - 不。
- Yeah. - Wha?
- 是的。 - 什么？
- Uh-huh. [both shriek]
- 嗯哼。 [两人尖叫]
- What are they saying? - I don't know.
他们在说什么？我不知道。
I need to learn this language.
我需要学习这种语言。
You should totes go get your losh on.
你应该去尽情享受你的洛什。
I don't like Loshawn.
我不喜欢洛肖恩。
I like Jaymis.
我喜欢杰米斯。
Whatevs. Dip out.
随便啦。溜了。
- I'll cover for you. - For real?
我会帮你打掩护。真的吗？
So fa.
到目前为止。
- T ya. - Welcs.
再见。欢迎。
See ya.
再见。
Move.
让开。
Now we just have to pick through a little box of clothes.
现在我们只需要从一个小箱子里挑些衣服。
Or a really big one.
或者一个非常大的箱子。
[whistling theme plays]
[口哨主题播放]
Tom, do you think the kids are okay out there?
汤姆，你觉得孩子们在外面还好吗？
[sighs]
[叹气]
Tom?
汤姆？
Tom!
汤姆！
What--no!
什么——不！
This is the best store in the mall.
这是商场里最好的店。
Dicky, this is the Lost and Found.
迪基，这里是失物招领处。
But they have everything here!
但他们这里什么都有！
We're only here for your pants.
我们只是来帮你找裤子的。
Hey, guys, look what I found.
嘿，伙计们，看我找到了什么。
These must be from the joke store.
这些肯定是来自那家恶搞商店的。
I don't think they are.
我不觉得是。
So this is real spinach?
所以这是真的菠菜？
Ahh!
啊！
[hums]
（哼唱）
♪ Sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
♪ 大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！♪
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被听见 ♪
[hums]
♪ Sing out loud! ♪
♪ 大声唱出来！♪
♪ Sing-- ♪ Oh, hey, Randee.
♪ 唱—— ♪ 哦，嘿，Randee。
I'm just here to clear out the Lost and Found bin.
我只是来清理失物招领箱的。
Did you see a teenage girl standing here?
你看到一个十几岁的女孩站在这里吗？
- Nope. - Huh. Weird.
- 没有。 - 嗯。奇怪。
- So am I good to go? - What do I care?
- 那我可以走了吗？ - 我怎么知道？
[both] ♪ La, la, la, la-- ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦—— ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦 ♪
How do so many people lose their pants?
怎么会有这么多人丢掉裤子？
I'm telling you, once you go Chunk,
我告诉你，一旦你尝试了Chunk，
you never go junk!
你就再也不会选择垃圾货了！
[engine revs]
[引擎轰鸣]
Uh, what's that?
呃，那是什么？
- What's happening? - We're about to be emptied
- 发生什么事了？ - 我们马上就要被倒进那辆卡车的后车厢了！
into the back of that truck!
- 我们得离开这里！ - 我的裤子！
- We gotta get out of here! - My pants!
- 抓住它们！ - 啊！
- Grab 'em! - Aah!
不！
No!
Great. Now we'll never find Mom's note.
太好了，现在我们永远找不到妈妈的纸条了。
Yes, we will. I got us into this mess.
会的，我们会的。是我把我们卷入这个麻烦的。
I'll get us out.
我会带我们出去的。
Tell my story!
告诉我的故事！
[all] Dicky!
迪基！
He's gone.
他走了。
- What are we gonna tell Mom? - His story.
我们要告诉妈妈什么？
I guess I'm the cool one now.
他的故事。
[gasps] He did it! He got the jeans!
我想我现在是酷的那一个了。
[grunts] I can't make it.
他做到了！他拿到了牛仔裤！
My skirt is caught.
我的裙子被卡住了。
Just take the pants.
直接拿裤子吧。
No, we are not leaving here without you.
不行，我们不会丢下你不管的。
Grab my hand!
抓住我的手！
- I can't reach. - Use the jeans!
- 我够不着。 - 用那条牛仔裤！
Throw us a leg!
扔条腿过来！
These cheap things?
这些便宜货？
- What if they rip? - But what if they don't?
- 万一撕破了怎么办？ - 但万一没撕破呢？
[grunting]
（用力声）
[panting]
（喘气声）
Oh, we did it!
哦，我们成功了！
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're awesome.
是啊，是啊，是啊，我们太棒了。
Grab the note.
拿上那张纸条。
Uh-oh. No note.
哎呀，没有纸条。
What do you mean, "no note"?
你说‘没有纸条’是什么意思？
We're supposed to be back in five minutes
我们本应该在五分钟内回去的，
and we have no idea what we're supposed to get Dad.
但我们根本不知道该给爸爸买什么。
Did any of you listen to what Mom said?
你们有人听到妈妈说什么了吗？
Uh, she said something about sweet, sweet mall chicks.
呃，她好像提到了甜美的商场女孩。
We're doomed.
我们完蛋了。
But what if we're... not?
但如果我們...不是呢？
Okay, I think that's one too many.
好吧，我覺得這已經太多了。
[chime] Customer 51.
[叮鈴] 第51位顧客。
51! 51 right here.
51！51在這裡。
Make a hole!
讓開！
Okay, I'm having some problems with my apps.
好的，我的應用程序出了一些問題。
- We're back! - Safe and sound.
- 我們回來了！- 安然無恙。
Oh, hey, Dad, we got your burger--ito--pizza-
哦，嘿，爸爸，我們給你買了漢堡-捲-披薩-
on a stick--wich?
在棍子上的-三明治？
Food in mouth, now!
現在就把食物塞進嘴裡！
Oh. Mmm. [chimes]
哦。嗯。[叮当声]
Customer 52.
顾客52。
[mumbles]
[含糊不清地说]
Sorry, sir, you stepped away from the counter.
对不起，先生，您离开了柜台。
- Take another number. - [mumbling]
- 再拿一个号码。 - [含糊不清地说]
Wow, I'm impressed, guys.
哇，我印象深刻，伙计们。
You obviously listened.
你们显然听进去了。
Aw, I'm so proud of you.
哦，我真为你们骄傲。
- Thanks. - Nailed it.
- 谢谢。 - 做到了。
Told you you could trust us.
告诉你你可以信任我们。
Wearing pants.
穿着裤子。
Just one question.
只有一个问题。
Where did you get the money to pay for all this?
你们是从哪里弄到钱来支付这一切的？
Because a burger-ito-pizza-on-a-stick-wich
因为一个汉堡-玉米卷-披萨-串-三明治
costs way more than $20.
花费远不止20美元。
[all] Uhh...
[所有人]呃...
Come on, spill it.
快说，坦白吧。
Fine. We split up, spent the money,
好吧。我们分头行动，花了钱，
lost the note you gave Dicky--
弄丢了你给迪基的纸条——
I checked all my pockets, but--
我检查了所有的口袋，但是——
Oh.
哦。
You had it there the whole time?
你一直把它放在那里吗？
I don't know about the whole time,
我不确定是不是一直都在，
but what matters is it's there now.
但重要的是它现在在那里。
"If you have any problems, just come back.
“如果你有任何问题，尽管回来。
No questions asked."
不问任何问题。”
Which you would have known, if you'd been listening.
如果你当时在听的话，你就会知道。
So if we'd come back, you wouldn't have been mad?
所以如果我们回来，你不会生气吗？
- No. - Are you mad now?
不会。
At your babies?
你现在生气吗？
[all mewling]
[全部在喵喵叫]
Oh, yeah. And disappointed.
哦，是的。还有失望。
Until you kids learn to listen--
直到你们这些孩子学会听话——
You're not listening now, are you?
你现在就没在听，对吧？
It's gonna take some practice.
这需要一些练习。
- 99. - We're gonna be here all night.
- 99. - 我们今晚要在这里待一整夜。
But what if we're not?
但如果我们不在呢？
♪ Sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
♪ 大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！♪
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
♪ 每个声音都值得被聆听 ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, every voice is beautiful ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，每个声音都很美妙 ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la ♪ - Go, go, go, go! - ♪ Every noise is musical, la, la, la, la, la ♪
啦啦啦啦 - 加油，加油，加油，加油！ 啦啦啦啦啦
♪ Every song you sing is gold ♪
你唱的每一首歌都是金子
♪ So sing out loud, sing out proud! ♪
所以大声唱出来，自豪地唱出来！
♪ Every voice deserves a crowd ♪
每个声音都值得被聆听
♪ La, la, la, la, every voice is beautiful ♪
啦啦啦啦，每个声音都是美丽的
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
啦啦啦啦
♪ Every noise is musical, la, la, la, la, la ♪
每个声音都是音乐，啦啦啦啦啦
♪ Every breath you take is precious ♪
你呼吸的每一口气都是宝贵的
♪ La la la la la ♪
啦啦啦啦啦
♪ Every song you sing is gold ♪
你唱的每一首歌都是金子
♪ La la la la la la la la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦 啦啦啦啦 ♪